(Howard:)We could snap a rubber
band on our wrists
(Howard:)every time we
get sidetracked.
(Sheldon:)Mmm, not bad.
You know, in medieval times,
(Sheldon:)idle chatter was punished
with a device called
(Sheldon:)the scold's bridle.
(Sheldon:)It's an iron cage
(Sheldon:)that's locked around the head
and pierces the tongue.
(Leonard:)If only we had one.
Oh! I'll check Amazon.
(knocking on door)
BERNADETTE:
Housekeeping!
AMY:
We had a complaint
(Amy:)about somebody pooping
on a party in there!
It was us the whole time!
(Amy:)Why'd you tell her?
It was working.
(Bernadette:)Was it working?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Bernadette:)Oh, I'm so sorry.
(Penny:)You guys look
like you're having fun.
(Amy:)We're having
the best time.
Guess who won $100
playing craps.